<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | ICSNLab</title>
    <link>https://example.com/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital twins of optical networks</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/dt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/dt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Digital twins has earned its reputation in manufactures, optical networks could also benefit from its digital twin, which is built upon the historical record, physical model and real-time monitoring data of the optical network in real world. The most important application of digital twins is to perform experiments on this digital replica rather than the real system, which helps reduce the risk and provides opptunity for bolder attempt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are establishing framework for digital twins of optical system, novel architectures and efficient algorithms are being expected.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain adaption in optical transmission system</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/da/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/da/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When deploying network control or prediction algorithms, it is often faced with mild or drastic environmental changes. One kind of uncertainty comes from the change of the external environment itself over time, and the other comes from the topology change of the network itself. We work on developing a domain adaption paradigm that minimizes the impact of environmental changes on algorithm performance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topological photonic crystal applications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/ayubing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/ayubing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Analogizing the topological phase of matter with substitutes in optics, topological photonics can make the transmission of light highly robust, which can be immune to some defects in the manufacturing process of integrated photonic devices. Two dimensional photonic crystal is the most common platform to realize topological photonic effect. Through some geometric design of topological PhC, some common photonic devices can be realized, which can be applied to communication, sensing, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality of transmission estimation</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;QoT estimation has always been a crucial task for optical communication systems, by predicting the transmission OSNR, BER or any other indicator of quality, the desiners could know whether the link is trustworthy or not in advance, they can take actions such as change the route or give higher system margin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;QoT estimation has been studied for years, however we are still facing some challenges. Modern optical networks are dynamic and running in ultra high speed, the conventional QoT estimation methods remains to be statical and lack of efficiency. Our research in QoT estimation tries to propose novel methods using the state-of-the-art model for addressing such challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
